[
    {
        "question": "1.What is RPA?",
        "answer": "Robotic Process Automation (RPA) is a software technology that makes it simple to create, deploy, and manage manual work using software robots that mimic human behavior while dealing with digital systems and software. It enables organizations to automate tasks across applications and systems in the same way that a human would. The goal of RPA is to move process execution away from people and toward bots.\nBe UiPath Certification ready. Enroll in RPA Training in Perth offered by Intellipaat.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "2.What is the UiPath tool?",
        "answer": "UiPath is a robotic process automation tool for large-scale end-to-end automation. Daniel Dines, a Romanian entrepreneur, created the company in 2005. It automates time-consuming processes and can be used with a variety of instruments. For rapid business transformation, UiPath software provides solutions for businesses to automate repetitive office operations. It uses a variety of techniques to turn tedious jobs into automated processes.\nBe UiPath Certification ready. Enroll in RPA Training in New York offered by Intellipaat",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "3.What are the various products of UiPath?",
        "answer": "These are the various products of UiPath. \nUiPath Studio: It is a user-friendly interface within the product that allows users to visually plan and construct different automation processes using diagrams. These diagrams are merely a structural depiction of specific tasks that must be completed. With the help of various diagrams, we may arrange any automation process visually. Each diagram depicts a specific type of task to be completed.\nUiPath Robot: After designing the procedure, the next step is to put it into action in the UiPath studio. UiPath Robots are used to turn the processes into tasks, which are then executed. These robots are used to assign various tasks and carry them out in the same manner as humans but without the need for human intervention. When a delegated job is assigned to an UiPath robot, it is meant to begin executing it automatically.\nUiPath Orchestrator: It is a web-based application in UiPath. It has features for deploying, monitoring, scheduling, and controlling software bots and processes. It’s a centralized platform that manages and controls all software bots.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "4.What are the various phases of an RPA life cycle?",
        "answer": "Various phases of the RPA life cycle are:\n\nThe first phase of an RPA life cycle is Identification and analysis. In which the RPA developers identify which business process will be automated. Once the process has been identified, it will be analyzed by RPA architects to decide the solution for their process, its complexity, and how to proceed with the project further.\nIn the development phase, the developers concentrate on the project requirements and develop the bot according to the type of automation. \nAfter the development of the RPA bot, it will be tested and sent for deployment in the Testing Phase.  \nAfter testing, it will be sent for deployment. After that, it goes through maintenance and updating.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. Explain UiPath architecture?",
        "answer": "The UiPath architecture is represented in the following image:\n\nUiPath Architecture has two sides and three layers. Which are the Client Side, Server Side and Client layer/presentation layer, Service layer, and persistence layer.\nClient-Side and Server Side: The Client-side has UiPath Studio, UiPath Robot, Browser, and UiPath Agent which are the most common client-side applications. The server-side handles the backend functions of UiPath Architecture.\nClient Layer/ Presentation Layer: The client layer is made up of UiPath components that may be accessed by users.\nServer Layer: The server layer shows all server information. The UiPath Orchestrator is the most important component of the server layer.\nPersistence Layer: Database servers make up the majority of persistence layers. This layer stores all of the robot’s configuration information.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. Mention the workflows in UiPath?",
        "answer": "UiPath has various workflows. When creating a workflow file, UiPath provides four diagrams for combining activities into a functioning structure. The four workflows are: \nFlowchart \nGlobal Exception Handler \nState Machine\nSequence",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. Explain the features of UiPath?",
        "answer": "The UiPath features are:\nSets of activities that are pre-defined\nDrag and drop the workflow\nPlayback and recording\nAutomation that is both attended and unattended\nReusability and workflow templates\nMulti-tenancy is a term that refers to a situation\nC# and.NET functions can be inherited.\nNo programming skills are required to use RPA technologies.\nProcess automation scheduling that is intelligent",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. Name the popular tools of RPA?",
        "answer": "The popular tools of RPA are:\nUiPath \nAutomation Anywhere \nBlue Prism.\nLaserfiche.\nPega Platform.\nAppian.\nWinAutomation by Softomotive.\nAutomate Robotic Process Automation.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Mention the advantages and disadvantages of RPA?",
        "answer": "The following are some of the advantages of RPA: \nRPA is simple to grasp. As it requires no coding skills, anyone can learn RPA easily.\nRPA offers high efficiency in terms of cost as compared to humans. Because human labor will be reduced by using RPA.\nRPA can meet the standards of the needs without errors. Hence it enhances quality control.\nBy using RPA, we can reduce human errors which lead to the productivity improvements\nAnother advantage of RPA is unlike humans, RPA bots can work in any circumstances. \nThe disadvantages of RPA are:\nUsing RPA in companies can cause job losses for employees.\nRPA automation is expensive. So it needs high-cost Initial Investment\nWorking with RPA needs high experts. But recruiting skilled professionals can be difficult.\nRPA cannot be suitable for all the processes. Only repetition work or work that does not involve human intervention can be done by RPA.\nWant to learn more about RPA check out our course on RPA Training in Wynwood.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. Describe the difference between UiPath and automation anywhere?",
        "answer": "UiPath  Automation Anywhere\nIt is used to model an organization’s business processes in a visual way. Automation Anywhere is a more script-based tool\nIt is a cloud-based architecture It is a client-server based architecture\nEffective and entry-level pricing High-cost deployment\nBoth browser and mobile access are available in UiPath It offers access to applications only\nOnly for small projects scalability is needed. For both small and medium projects, Highly scalability is needed.\nCheck out this video on the UiPath tutorial:",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "11. What is the difference between UiPath and Blue Prism?",
        "answer": "UiPath Blue Prism\nTakes time to install the software. Easy to install.\nOffers best visual design features. Offers the best control features.\nWorks on the basis of RPA’s attended mode of robot. Works on the basis of RPA’s unattended robot mode.\nUiPath has High-speed mapping processes. It does not have High-speed mapping processes. \nProvides access for both mobile and browser.  Provides access for only apps.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "12. Give some examples of automation that can be done using UiPath?",
        "answer": "Using UiPath, we can work on repetitive tasks, we can move files from one source to another source, we can also work on various automation such as Web Automation, Email Automation, Excel Automation, PDF Automation, etc.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "13. What are the various types of recordings present in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Desktop, Basic, Web, Image, and Citrix are various types of recordings in UiPath.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "14. What are the major advantages of UiPath?",
        "answer": "The advantages of UiPath are:\nThe UiPath can be accessed through mobile and browser.\nThe key benefit of the UiPath tool for developing an effective digital workforce is its flexibility. UiPath is highly flexible. \nWith UiPath practices, productivity can be increased.\nThe UiPath tool’s ecosystem has been optimized for faster development and is designed to provide a quick return on investment.\nCompanies that are using UiPath can provide the best possible customer experience.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "15. What is the value and scope of data types?",
        "answer": "A variable is a type of data storage. You can also change the variable’s value. When data is saved in a variable, the value can be of many different types. There are numerous data kinds in UiPath, including text numbers, generic values, time, date, and data tables.\nThat is all in the section of Basic UiPath practice questions. Let’s move on to the next section of UiPath intermediate Interview Questions.\n\n\nIntermediate UiPath Interview Questions and Answers\nIn this section, we are going to discuss the intermediate level Interview Questions for the UiPath developer",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "16. How to create a project and execute it in UiPath studio?",
        "answer": "We can create a project with just a few steps such as:\nStep 1: In the UiPath studio software, click the Start button. After that Choose a project type. To start a new project, enter the name, location, and description in the new tab and click the Create button.\nStep 2: Include the web page and Excel file in the automation.\nStep 3: Enter the activities to be completed in the browser and Excel.\nStep 4: Then finally, select Run to Execute the automation.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "17. What are the different types of variable error handling actions in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Exception Handling is primarily concerned with handling errors in UiPath’s many actions. There are four possibilities for the Error Handling activity which are Terminate workflow, Try Catch, Throw, and Catch.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "18. What is Branching?",
        "answer": "In UiPath, branching is referred to as a “condition.” This statement will assist the software in determining what to do when a condition is selected. When an activity has more than one solution following a given condition, this condition is used. This condition statement will assist the software in determining what behavior should be displayed.\nLearn RPA with Intellipaat’s tutorial blog to gain more knowledge about RPA.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "19. What is Delay activity?",
        "answer": "You can use the Delay activity to pause the automation for a specific amount of time (in the hh:mm:ss format). This activity comes in handy when working on projects that require precise timing, such as waiting for a certain application to start or for data to be processed before using it in another activity.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "20. Why do we use element exist in UiPath?",
        "answer": "During the execution of a program in UiPath, the Element exist is used to determine whether the UI element is there or not. It only supports boolean.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "21. What is the difference between While activity and Do-while activity?",
        "answer": "Whereas If a condition is met, the Do While action allows you to perform a specific component of your project. The automation exits the loop when the given condition is no longer met. The key difference between this and the Do While activity is that the condition is evaluated before the loop’s body is executed in the first one.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "22. What is Assign activity?",
        "answer": "The Assign activity is a crucial one that will be used frequently since it allows you to assign a value to a variable.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "23. What is Switch activity?",
        "answer": "The Switch activity allows you to choose one option from a list of several based on the value of an expression. The integer argument is used by default in the Switch activity, but you may alter it in the Properties panel’s TypeArgument list. The Switch activity can be used to sort data into groups based on a specified number of cases.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "24. Mention the difference between Screen Scraping and Data scraping?",
        "answer": "Screen Scraping Data Scraping\nScreen Scraping is only used for extracting unstructured data.  Data Scraping is only used for extracting structured data.\nIt stores the scrapped information in a data table. It stores the scrapped information in a string.\nWith screen scraping, it is difficult to extract data into Excel or a database. Data scraping can easily export data to excel or a database\nScreen Scraping can collect data by extracting from images and PDF. Whereas Data Scraping cannot extract from images and  PDF.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "25. What are Arguments in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Data can be passed from one project to another through arguments. They are similar to variables in that they store data dynamically and pass it on. Arguments pass data between automation, whereas variables pass data between activities. As a result, you can reuse some projects over and over again.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "26. What are a thin client and a thick client in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Thin client: Any application in which we are unable to obtain high-quality properties when spying (using any RPA tool). Citrix or any virtual environment can be said as an example.\nThick Client: Any application with a large number of attribute properties qualifies (using RPA tools). for example, Calculator and Internet Explorer.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "27. Do you know about Citrix automation?",
        "answer": "The virtual machine is a computer science emulator. If you want to process automation in Citrix machines efficiently, you’ll require approaches and tools. The virtual machine is operated via Citrix automation in UiPath.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "28. What is PDF automation?",
        "answer": "A PDF is a file format used to capture and send electronic documents in their original format. And creating or reading such files and fetching the information from the PDFs is known as PDF automation.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "29. What is Email Automation?",
        "answer": "The capacity to send relevant information to subscribers in response to time or action-triggered emails is known as Email Automation.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "30. Mention the types of OCR engines available which can integrate with UiPath?",
        "answer": "In UiPath you can find several OCR engines. Which are Google cloud OCR, Google OCR, Microsoft Cloud OCR, Microsoft OCR, and Abbyy Cloud OCR.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "31. Mention the types of robots in RPA?",
        "answer": "Businesses can use two types of robots to automate certain processes. Which are the Traditional RPA and the Cognitive RPA.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "32. In UiPath, what is a state machine?",
        "answer": "A state machine is a sort of automation that executes with a limited number of states. It can enter a state when triggered by an activity and exit that state when triggered by another activity. Transitions are another significant feature of state machines since they allow you to add criteria to jump from one state to another. Arrows or branches are used to depict between the states.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "33. Mention the key difference between process automation and test automation?",
        "answer": "To finish a task, Process Automation that mimics human behaviors. RPA is used to automate processes in the corporate environment without requiring human interaction, while Test Automation is used for testing purposes while automating any application to assess product quality.\nCheck out these top RPA Interview Questions by Intellipaat.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "34. In UiPath studio, which activity can be utilized to iterate through an activity?",
        "answer": "In UiPath Studio, we may utilize “For each activity and While activity” to cycle through an activity.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "35. What is debugging in UiPath?",
        "answer": "In the automation of UiPath, Debugging is the process of locating and resolving application issues and errors. This process is used to ensure that the applications have no errors. It has both breakpoints and logging, making debugging automation easier. Breakpoints are helpful to take a break in the project’s execution so that the state we can check at each certain point. Logging, on the other hand, allows you to see details about what’s going on in your project in the Output panel.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "36. In UiPath, how do you convert a string to an integer?",
        "answer": "In UiPath, you may use the following method to convert a string to an integer.\nConvert.ToInt32(String variable_name)",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "37. What is UiPath Explorer?",
        "answer": "UI Explorer is UiPath’s most powerful tool for creating a customize selector for a specific UI element. You can get this through your Automation Cloud instance’s Resource Center, or from Studio if you have the UiPath.UIAutomation.Activities package is installed as a project dependency.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "38. What is Computer vision activity?",
        "answer": "We can allow the UiPath Robots to view every aspect of an interface with the help of AI-based Computer Vision. You may quickly create vision-based automation and edit them globally that works on any virtual desktop interface environment—regardless of framework or operating system.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "39. What is the append range in UiPath?",
        "answer": "In UiPath, Append ranges are used to insert, add, or alter the data into an existing worksheet. We can insert data after the last written data from the workbook using append ranges. Additionally, previous data will not be overwritten when new data is appended to a file.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "40. What are the various types of variables in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Text Variables.\nTrue or False Variables.\nNumber Variables.\nArray Variables.\nDate and Time Variables.\nData Table Variables.\nCheck out this video on RPA training:\n\n\n\n\nAdvanced UiPath Interview Questions for Experienced\nHere comes Advanced UiPath developer Interview Questions which will be very helpful to crack the interview. So go ahead and read.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "41. What is the procedure for activating an UiPath Studio license?",
        "answer": "The following are the steps you need to perform to activate the UiPath Studio license.\nTo activate your license, you need to click the Activate License button first. The registration window for UiPath appears.\nFill enter your email address in the Email Address field.\nEnter the license key you received in the License Key area.\nSelect the option for automatic activation.\nThen press the Activate button.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "42. What is the contention in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Contention urges the application to make a few arguments in which you can also implement changes. In disputes, you must give the name, which is required. Expound on the route and choose the type of contention: string, object, Int 32, or cluster.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "43. In UiPath, what are UI Activities Properties?",
        "answer": "In UiPath automation, several UI activity properties may be used to automate apps or web apps. All of these activities have a various number of characteristics in common, which are listed below:\nContinueOnError – This property indicates whether the automation should continue even if an error occurs during the action. Only boolean values are accepted in this field. It has true and false values. In which the field’s default value is False. As a result, if this field is left blank and an error is given, the project’s execution is halted. If the value is set to True, the project will continue to run even if there is an error.\nDelay After – Delay After property adds a milliseconds-long pause after the activity.\nDelay Before – It adds a millisecond wait before the activity.\nTimeout MS – Timeout MS is the amount of time (in milliseconds) to wait for a particular element to be discovered before throwing an error. 30000 milliseconds is the default setting (30 seconds).\nTarget – The activity’s target is the UI element with which it interacts.\nWaitForReady – WaitForReady is a property that is used to Wait for the target to become ready before conducting the actions. To guarantee that you correctly identify a UI element, the target is made up of various elements, including the container, selector, and clipping region.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "44. Mention the different ways to create a variable in UiPath.",
        "answer": "The following are the various ways to create a variable in UiPath:\nProperties Pane -> Output Section -> Right-click the mouse and select Create variable / CTRL + K \nControl Bar -> Select the Variables Tab -> Make a variable\nOr you can choose to create a variable from the Ribbon Tab.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "45. How can I connect the database to UiPath and read data from it?",
        "answer": "To connect the database to UiPath, follow the instructions below.\nYou must first install the Database activities package. The Package Manager can be used to install this package.\nYou may now utilize the “Connect” activity to establish a link between UiPath studio and the database.\nThen, to configure the connection, click the “Configure Connection” button.\nSelect the necessary connection settings and perform a connection test. When the test connection is successful, click OK.\nUse the “Execute Query” activity to write your required SQL query to read data once the connection has been created.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "46. In UiPath, explain the terms read range, read cell, read csv, write range, write cell, and write csv.",
        "answer": "Read range – It is used to read data from an excel spreadsheet.\nRead cell — This command is used to read all of the data from the specified cell.\nWrite range – It can be used to write data on an excel sheet. Read csv – It can be used to read all csv data.\nWrite cell – We may use write cell to write data into a certain column.\nWrite csv — This command is used to save data in a csv format.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "47. If the Package Manager’s tested package is not accessible, Do you know how to get the desired package in UiPath studio?",
        "answer": "To get the desired package in UiPath Studio. First, go to this proxy site. This will provide a list of all the packages, along with their URLs and most recent versions. Then, navigate to the URL followed by the package name and save it to your computer’s hard disc. Then, in the UiPath package manager, right-click any of the nodes.\nThen Configure Sources will appear, and you’ll need to point it to the place where the package was obtained locally. The UiPath package manager will now show all of the downloaded packages. Now you can proceed to install the package using the UiPath package manager as usual.",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "48. In UiPath, what do you mean by Selectors and Wildcards?",
        "answer": "In UiPath, Wildcards are characters that can be used to substitute one or more characters in a string. When dealing with dynamically changing properties in a selector, these might be very beneficial. wildcards can be used to replace zero or more characters in a string.\nIn UiPath studio, the following wildcard characters are supported for selectors: Asterisk (*) –n replace one or more characters in a string. A single character is replaced by a question mark (?).",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "49. How to connect robots to orchestrators in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Connect a robot to orchestrators as described here\nClick the UiPath Robot icon in the system tray which is visible there.\nSelect Orchestrator Settings from the Settings menu.\nEnter the key received from the user who created the Robot in Orchestrator in the Machine Key section (as obtained from the Machines page).\nEnter the Orchestrator URL in the Orchestrator URL area. Make sure to include the AccountLogicalName and ServiceName if you’re using one of your Cloud Platform Services, such as\nhttp://platform.UiPath.com/[AccountLogicalName]/[ServiceName]/\nConnect by clicking the Connect button. The Robot is now connected to Orchestrator and has the status of being available. When a Robot is added to Orchestrator, a Robot user is created and the Robot role is assigned to them. (It’s available on the Users page.)",
        "reference": "intellipaat.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "1. What do you mean by generic variable in UiPath?",
        "answer": "The generic variable in UiPath is a sort of variable that can handle a wide range of data types. Arrays, ints, strings, and date formats, for example.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. Why is UiPath the most preferred RPA tool in industry?",
        "answer": "UiPath is a business process automation tool created specifically for enterprise computing. According to industry standards, a wide range of distinctive features and functionalities are available. The following are some features that set UiPath apart from other RPA tools: The Entire Package: With the help of three components, UiPath Studio, UiPath Orchestrator, and UiPath Robots, UiPath provides a full solution.\nIntuitive: Because it combines drag and drop and flowchart activities, working with UiPath and developing robots is fairly intuitive. It's also incredibly simple to learn.\nA large number of activities are available in the library: UiPath has a large activity library that includes hundreds of pre-built drag-and-drop activities.\nSecurity: Because we can store and encrypt credentials on a centralized server, UiPath provides a high level of security.\nRecording: UiPath also has the capability of recording. It contains dedicated recorders for desktop apps, Citrix environments, and terminal emulators, allowing for considerably faster and more exact automation creation.\nUniversal Search: It has a universal search capability that allows us to search across all automation resources such as libraries, activities, projects, and workflows in a single search.\nDebugging Techniques: UiPath provides users with a robust debugging tool that is both intuitive and adaptable.\nCollaboration: Because we can save, secure, and exchange scripts in MS Team Foundation and SVN, UiPath encourages collaboration. The workflow can also be reused.\nIntegration with third parties: UiPath also offers third-party integration services. At the API level, we may integrate numerous cognitive and OCR technologies from ABBYY, IBM Watson, Google, and Microsoft text analysis.\nLicensing on the Server: Uipath supports server-based licensing, which centralizes and simplifies the licensing procedure. The Entire Package: With the help of three components, UiPath Studio, UiPath Orchestrator, and UiPath Robots, UiPath provides a full solution. The Entire Package Intuitive: Because it combines drag and drop and flowchart activities, working with UiPath and developing robots is fairly intuitive. It's also incredibly simple to learn. Intuitive: A large number of activities are available in the library: UiPath has a large activity library that includes hundreds of pre-built drag-and-drop activities. A large number of activities are available in the library: Security: Because we can store and encrypt credentials on a centralized server, UiPath provides a high level of security. Security: Recording: UiPath also has the capability of recording. It contains dedicated recorders for desktop apps, Citrix environments, and terminal emulators, allowing for considerably faster and more exact automation creation. Recording: Universal Search: It has a universal search capability that allows us to search across all automation resources such as libraries, activities, projects, and workflows in a single search. Universal Search: Debugging Techniques: UiPath provides users with a robust debugging tool that is both intuitive and adaptable. Debugging Techniques: Collaboration: Because we can save, secure, and exchange scripts in MS Team Foundation and SVN, UiPath encourages collaboration. The workflow can also be reused. Collaboration: Integration with third parties: UiPath also offers third-party integration services. At the API level, we may integrate numerous cognitive and OCR technologies from ABBYY, IBM Watson, Google, and Microsoft text analysis. Integration with third parties: Licensing on the Server: Uipath supports server-based licensing, which centralizes and simplifies the licensing procedure. Licensing on the Server:  ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. What are the components of UiPath?",
        "answer": "The three primary components of UiPath are as follows:   UiPath Studio: It is a graphical user interface (GUI) dashboard for automating workflows. It comes with a variety of tools and settings, making it a one-stop-shop for workflow creation. Each process indicates a certain task to be completed.\nUiPath Robots (also known as bots): They are the most basic component of the UiPath tool. They're primarily used to run automation processes written in UiPath Studio. These robots can also be used to begin the execution of tasks automatically in response to any specified activity on the system.\nUiPath Orchestrator: It is a web-based tool for deploying, scheduling, monitoring, and managing UiPath robots in the environment. It's the centralized platform for managing and controlling software robots. It serves as a link between UiPath Studio and UiPath robots. UiPath Studio: It is a graphical user interface (GUI) dashboard for automating workflows. It comes with a variety of tools and settings, making it a one-stop-shop for workflow creation. Each process indicates a certain task to be completed. UiPath Studio: UiPath Robots (also known as bots): They are the most basic component of the UiPath tool. They're primarily used to run automation processes written in UiPath Studio. These robots can also be used to begin the execution of tasks automatically in response to any specified activity on the system. UiPath Robots (also known as bots): UiPath Orchestrator: It is a web-based tool for deploying, scheduling, monitoring, and managing UiPath robots in the environment. It's the centralized platform for managing and controlling software robots. It serves as a link between UiPath Studio and UiPath robots. UiPath Orchestrator:",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. Explain the different types of workflows present in UiPath.",
        "answer": "The workflow types in UiPath are as follows: Sequences: A sequence is a tiny project that works best with linear processes. It makes it simple for developers to go from one activity to another. It can be used as many times as necessary.\nState Machine: A state machine is a machine that uses a specific amount of states to automate the execution time. By activating a specific action, it can be shifted from one state to another.\nFlowchart: A flowchart is a graphical depiction of several automated operations. It's useful for integrating the activities in huge projects and developing complex business tasks. Flowcharts can also aid in the display of many logical operator branching.\nGlobal Exception Handler: The Exception Handler is intended for use in both small and large automation projects, with the goal of discovering execution problems and, more significantly, deciding the workflow action when they occur. If an execution error occurs while debugging, the Global Exception Handler can be configured to intervene and check the workflow's behavior using the options previously provided in the Exception Handler. Sequences: A sequence is a tiny project that works best with linear processes. It makes it simple for developers to go from one activity to another. It can be used as many times as necessary. Sequences: State Machine: A state machine is a machine that uses a specific amount of states to automate the execution time. By activating a specific action, it can be shifted from one state to another. State Machine: Flowchart: A flowchart is a graphical depiction of several automated operations. It's useful for integrating the activities in huge projects and developing complex business tasks. Flowcharts can also aid in the display of many logical operator branching. Flowchart: Global Exception Handler: The Exception Handler is intended for use in both small and large automation projects, with the goal of discovering execution problems and, more significantly, deciding the workflow action when they occur. If an execution error occurs while debugging, the Global Exception Handler can be configured to intervene and check the workflow's behavior using the options previously provided in the Exception Handler. Global Exception Handler:",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. Where are the major applications of UiPath?",
        "answer": "The following are a few of UiPath's most common uses: Financial Reporting \nExtraction of data\nObtaining Market Information\nKeeping track of the customer dashboard Processing of Data Orders\nData Capture and Manipulation for Invoice Generation\nData Entry and Email Exchange\nGetting Data from a Variety of Sources\nUsing the System to Automate Daily Routine Tasks Financial Reporting Extraction of data Obtaining Market Information Keeping track of the customer dashboard Processing of Data Orders Data Capture and Manipulation for Invoice Generation Data Entry and Email Exchange Getting Data from a Variety of Sources Using the System to Automate Daily Routine Tasks",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. Is Robotic Process Automation the same as Artificial Intelligence?",
        "answer": "No, Robotic Process Automation is not the same as Artificial Intelligence. While Robotic Process Automation is meant to assist workers by automating repetitive tasks (attended automation), Artificial Intelligence is considered a technology that can replace human labor and automate end-to-end operations (unattended automation). AI uses unstructured inputs and develops its own reasoning, whereas RPA uses organized inputs and logic. A fully autonomous process can be created by combining RPA and artificial intelligence.   Many processes require both RPA and AI to fully automate a process from beginning to end or to improve a robotic process once it has been deployed because companies have both structured data (e.g., form fields) and unstructured data (e.g., free text, natural voice). RPA and AI work together to push automation into new domains, enabling users to automate more and more complicated activities.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. What do you mean by an attended bot?",
        "answer": "Attended bots are bots that work on the same computer as a human user and are typically activated by the user's actions (user events). On these types of Robots, you can't start processes from Orchestrator, and they can't run under a locked screen. They can only be launched from the Robot tray. Attended bots",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. What do you mean by an unattended bot?",
        "answer": "Bots that run unattended in virtual environments and can automate a variety of operations are known as unattended bots. This Robot is responsible for remote execution, monitoring, scheduling, and providing assistance for work queues, in addition to the features of the Attended Robot. unattended bots",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Differentiate between Attended RPA and Unattended RPA.",
        "answer": "  Attended RPA Bots Unattended RPA Bots\nAttended RPA bots act as virtual assistants, assisting a single employee with their responsibilities in order to increase productivity. Legacy Attended Automation is limited to the desktop of a single employee. Unattended RPA bots conduct self-contained automation. End-to-end automation, in which bots may perform full operations independently, is the goal for many corporate processes.\nCollaborates with employees and teams to assist with front-office activities. Back-office processes are automated at a large scale.\nAttended RPA bots are ready and waiting for employees to activate them anytime they are needed to speed up the process. Unattended RPA bots follow a set of instructions or are triggered by logic in the process flow.\nEmployees activate a bot and interact with it as it provides assistance. Managers can coordinate tasks across internal resources and coordinate tasks between people and machines. Unattended RPA bots complete tasks on their own, following a set of rules.\nIt increases efficiency and reduces average call handling time, which improves customer satisfaction and compliance. Operating costs are reduced. It boosts productivity. Errors are eliminated. Employees are relieved of monotonous tasks, which improves compliance. Attended RPA Bots Unattended RPA Bots\nAttended RPA bots act as virtual assistants, assisting a single employee with their responsibilities in order to increase productivity. Legacy Attended Automation is limited to the desktop of a single employee. Unattended RPA bots conduct self-contained automation. End-to-end automation, in which bots may perform full operations independently, is the goal for many corporate processes.\nCollaborates with employees and teams to assist with front-office activities. Back-office processes are automated at a large scale.\nAttended RPA bots are ready and waiting for employees to activate them anytime they are needed to speed up the process. Unattended RPA bots follow a set of instructions or are triggered by logic in the process flow.\nEmployees activate a bot and interact with it as it provides assistance. Managers can coordinate tasks across internal resources and coordinate tasks between people and machines. Unattended RPA bots complete tasks on their own, following a set of rules.\nIt increases efficiency and reduces average call handling time, which improves customer satisfaction and compliance. Operating costs are reduced. It boosts productivity. Errors are eliminated. Employees are relieved of monotonous tasks, which improves compliance. Attended RPA Bots Unattended RPA Bots Attended RPA Bots Unattended RPA Bots Attended RPA Bots Unattended RPA Bots Attended RPA bots act as virtual assistants, assisting a single employee with their responsibilities in order to increase productivity. Legacy Attended Automation is limited to the desktop of a single employee. Unattended RPA bots conduct self-contained automation. End-to-end automation, in which bots may perform full operations independently, is the goal for many corporate processes.\nCollaborates with employees and teams to assist with front-office activities. Back-office processes are automated at a large scale.\nAttended RPA bots are ready and waiting for employees to activate them anytime they are needed to speed up the process. Unattended RPA bots follow a set of instructions or are triggered by logic in the process flow.\nEmployees activate a bot and interact with it as it provides assistance. Managers can coordinate tasks across internal resources and coordinate tasks between people and machines. Unattended RPA bots complete tasks on their own, following a set of rules.\nIt increases efficiency and reduces average call handling time, which improves customer satisfaction and compliance. Operating costs are reduced. It boosts productivity. Errors are eliminated. Employees are relieved of monotonous tasks, which improves compliance. Attended RPA bots act as virtual assistants, assisting a single employee with their responsibilities in order to increase productivity. Legacy Attended Automation is limited to the desktop of a single employee. Unattended RPA bots conduct self-contained automation. End-to-end automation, in which bots may perform full operations independently, is the goal for many corporate processes. Attended RPA bots act as virtual assistants, assisting a single employee with their responsibilities in order to increase productivity. Legacy Attended Automation is limited to the desktop of a single employee. Unattended RPA bots conduct self-contained automation. End-to-end automation, in which bots may perform full operations independently, is the goal for many corporate processes. Collaborates with employees and teams to assist with front-office activities. Back-office processes are automated at a large scale. Collaborates with employees and teams to assist with front-office activities. Back-office processes are automated at a large scale. Attended RPA bots are ready and waiting for employees to activate them anytime they are needed to speed up the process. Unattended RPA bots follow a set of instructions or are triggered by logic in the process flow. Attended RPA bots are ready and waiting for employees to activate them anytime they are needed to speed up the process. Unattended RPA bots follow a set of instructions or are triggered by logic in the process flow. Employees activate a bot and interact with it as it provides assistance. Managers can coordinate tasks across internal resources and coordinate tasks between people and machines. Unattended RPA bots complete tasks on their own, following a set of rules. Employees activate a bot and interact with it as it provides assistance. Managers can coordinate tasks across internal resources and coordinate tasks between people and machines. Unattended RPA bots complete tasks on their own, following a set of rules. It increases efficiency and reduces average call handling time, which improves customer satisfaction and compliance. Operating costs are reduced. It boosts productivity. Errors are eliminated. Employees are relieved of monotonous tasks, which improves compliance. It increases efficiency and reduces average call handling time, which improves customer satisfaction and compliance. Operating costs are reduced. It boosts productivity. Errors are eliminated. Employees are relieved of monotonous tasks, which improves compliance.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. What is UiPath Explorer?",
        "answer": "The powerful tool UI Explorer allows users to construct a custom selector for a single UI element. It's a standalone utility that users can get from your Automation Cloud instance's Resource Center, or through Studio if you're using UiPath. The UIAutomation.The activities package is added to the project as a dependency.   You don't need to install Studio to use UI Explorer as a standalone application. This is useful when you want to ensure that a program can be automated using selectors. It allows you to quickly inspect items without having to create a process.\nThe SetupExtensions utility is included in the standalone package, allowing users to install browser extensions and the JavaBridge to examine items across all of the automation needs. ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "11. What do you mean by arguments in the context of UiPath?",
        "answer": "The arguments in UiPath are primarily used when data must be passed from one workflow to another. They are in charge of transferring data between projects. These arguments must follow a particular direction. For instance, in, out.  ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "12. What do you mean by Robotic Process Automation (RPA)?",
        "answer": "Robotic Process Automation (RPA) is a technology that allows work to be automated in the same way that a human would. Robotic process automation does not imply that robots would completely replace humans; rather, it refers to computer software that mimics human behaviors. Robotic Process Automation Robotic Process Automation   To put it another way, RPA is a software programme that imitates human activities while interacting with a computer application and automating repetitive and rule-based procedures. Back office activities, data entry, data validation, and other labor-intensive jobs can all be automated with RPA. The method enables businesses to automate their digital processes across multiple applications and systems without having to change their existing IT architecture. RPA can be broken down in the following way:- Robotic: A set of codes that mimics human movements and acts like a robot.P\nProcess: It is the collection of steps that results in a meaningful activity.\nAutomation: It is a procedure that is carried out by software robots without the involvement of humans. Robotic: A set of codes that mimics human movements and acts like a robot.P Robotic: Process: It is the collection of steps that results in a meaningful activity. Process Automation: It is a procedure that is carried out by software robots without the involvement of humans. Automation",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "13. What do you mean by session variables in the context of UiPath?",
        "answer": "Session variables in UiPath are defined as variables that are unique to a single instance of a process. If many instances of the corresponding process run at the same time, all of the session variables will be the same. The values for those session variables, on the other hand, will be different.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "14. What are the different properties in UiPath?",
        "answer": "UiPath provides a number of activities that aid in the automation of desktop and web-based applications. In the activity panel under UI automation, properties describe such activities that are utilized for automating apps. ContinueOnError, Delay Before, Delay After, TimeoutMS, Target, and WaitForReady are the core attributes of any project.   ContinueOnError: This is utilized when we want our automation to keep running even if there is an issue in the activity. The default value is 'False'. When an activity inside the 'try catch' is set to 'True,' the project will not show any errors.\nDelay Before: This command is used to pause the automation before doing a specified task.\nDelay After: This command is used to suspend the automation after completing a certain task.\nTimeoutMS: It's used to locate an element before an error message appears.\nTarget: Prior to the start of an activity, the target is used to identify the element. ContinueOnError: This is utilized when we want our automation to keep running even if there is an issue in the activity. The default value is 'False'. When an activity inside the 'try catch' is set to 'True,' the project will not show any errors. ContinueOnError: Delay Before: This command is used to pause the automation before doing a specified task. Delay Before: Delay After: This command is used to suspend the automation after completing a certain task. Delay After: TimeoutMS: It's used to locate an element before an error message appears. TimeoutMS: Target: Prior to the start of an activity, the target is used to identify the element. Target:",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "15. What do you mean by Branching in UiPath?",
        "answer": "In UiPath, branching is referred to as the 'condition.' When there is an activity with numerous solutions after a given condition, the branching condition is utilized. This branching allows the software to determine what behavior should be presented in the event that a specific condition is selected.\nSwitch Activity can be used to implement branching. The integer argument is used by default in the Switch activity, but you may alter it in the Properties panel's TypeArgument list. The Switch activity can be used to sort data into groups based on a specified number of cases.   ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "16. What is the importance of flowchart activities in UiPath?",
        "answer": "In UiPath, the flowchart activities allow us to manage the basic settings for any task. These tasks can be used for practically any form of the automation project, regardless of its duration or complexity. Flowcharts are also utilized in the automation of complicated corporate projects to separate and develop logical procedures. During the automation process, flowchart activities can be used to integrate necessary actions or functionalities into flowcharts.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "17. Explain the life cycle of RPA.",
        "answer": "The RPA Lifecycle encompasses several stages of the automation process, from bot creation to bot execution.   The following is a list of them: Discovery:  The discovery phase of the RPA lifecycle is the first step. The RPA process architect evaluates the client's needs in this phase. Then it's decided whether or not the procedure can be automated. If the process can be automated, the RPA analyst team may consult with the RPA architect team to assess the process's complexity.\nSolution Design: The steps to automate the process are defined based on the requirements. In conjunction with the process architect, the RPA technical architect creates a Process Definition Document (PDD) that contains information about the entire process. They adhere to the development methodology and devise a plan to automate certain tasks in order to eliminate manual labor as much as possible.\nAfter all of the requirements have been met, the next stage is to decide on a budget, the number of people who will work on the project, the amount of time that will be spent on it, and so on. The analyst team then constructs a flowchart to visualize the flow of operations, which aids in the selection of the appropriate processes for automation. The RPA tool is used to begin the development of bots and automate tasks after the procedures have been chosen.\nDevelopment: The RPA developer builds scripts/bots to automate tasks using RPA tools at this phase. There are a variety of RPA tools on the market. Following the previously created PDD, automation scripts/bots are generated. There is no demand for coding in most cases. However, depending on the duties to be automated, this may alter.\nUser Acceptance Tests: The RPA development team puts the bots they've created to the test in this phase. These bots are put through their paces in a test setting to see how they can help users automate specific chores. If the testing phase is completed successfully, the process moves on to the next level. Furthermore, if the testing fails, it is returned to the development phase, where RPA developers evaluate and correct any issues discovered during the testing phase.\nDeployment and Maintenance: Only when the development and testing phases have been finished are the bots deployed into the production environment. Users can utilize them to automate their tasks when the deployment procedure is completed. If a problem with the bots persists, such as bots that do not automate, they are forwarded to the RPA development and testing team. The bots will be analyzed again by the development team, and the issues will be resolved.\nBots Execution: After the bots have been deployed, this phase includes the bots' execution. Bots are also examined to guarantee that the implementation is carried out correctly. Discovery:  The discovery phase of the RPA lifecycle is the first step. The RPA process architect evaluates the client's needs in this phase. Then it's decided whether or not the procedure can be automated. If the process can be automated, the RPA analyst team may consult with the RPA architect team to assess the process's complexity. Discovery: Solution Design: The steps to automate the process are defined based on the requirements. In conjunction with the process architect, the RPA technical architect creates a Process Definition Document (PDD) that contains information about the entire process. They adhere to the development methodology and devise a plan to automate certain tasks in order to eliminate manual labor as much as possible.\nAfter all of the requirements have been met, the next stage is to decide on a budget, the number of people who will work on the project, the amount of time that will be spent on it, and so on. The analyst team then constructs a flowchart to visualize the flow of operations, which aids in the selection of the appropriate processes for automation. The RPA tool is used to begin the development of bots and automate tasks after the procedures have been chosen. Solution Design:  Development: The RPA developer builds scripts/bots to automate tasks using RPA tools at this phase. There are a variety of RPA tools on the market. Following the previously created PDD, automation scripts/bots are generated. There is no demand for coding in most cases. However, depending on the duties to be automated, this may alter. Development: User Acceptance Tests: The RPA development team puts the bots they've created to the test in this phase. These bots are put through their paces in a test setting to see how they can help users automate specific chores. If the testing phase is completed successfully, the process moves on to the next level. Furthermore, if the testing fails, it is returned to the development phase, where RPA developers evaluate and correct any issues discovered during the testing phase. User Acceptance Tests: Deployment and Maintenance: Only when the development and testing phases have been finished are the bots deployed into the production environment. Users can utilize them to automate their tasks when the deployment procedure is completed. If a problem with the bots persists, such as bots that do not automate, they are forwarded to the RPA development and testing team. The bots will be analyzed again by the development team, and the issues will be resolved. Deployment and Maintenance: Bots Execution: After the bots have been deployed, this phase includes the bots' execution. Bots are also examined to guarantee that the implementation is carried out correctly. Bots Execution:",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "18. What do you mean by Flow Switch in the context of UiPath?",
        "answer": "A FlowSwitch activity is similar to a FlowDecision, but it is not limited to a True or False branch. A FlowStep is a name for each branch of a FlowSwitch activity.\nWhen more than two alternative branches are required, the FlowSwitch activity is a conditional node that provides branching for the flow of control depending on a match condition. We use the FlowDecision activity instead if the flow branching only requires two pathways.\nWhen the Expression in the FlowSwitch<System.int32> activity is evaluated, it returns a value of type Int32. The activity additionally includes a set of Cases that define a unique mapping between the evaluation's possible outcomes to a set of FlowNode objects. The FlowNode that is executed is the one whose int32 object matches the evaluated Expression's value. For the case where no match is found, a default case might be specified (optionally).  ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "19. Explain switch activity in the context of UiPath.",
        "answer": "In UiPath, the switch activity is used to transition from one value to another based on the expression's defined values. As a default, it uses the switch integer argument. However, by navigating to the properties tab and selecting the needed Type of Argument, we can easily change it (TypeArgument). The activity is most useful when it comes to categorizing data by case number. This activity can be used to save data into different spreadsheets or to sort through a list of user names, for example.  ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "20. Does UiPath support automatic recording?",
        "answer": "Yes, UiPath allows us to automatically record the actions and activities we execute on the system. We can quickly personalize the project using the automatic recording tool, which provides a number of possibilities. It creates a skeleton of the entire procedure that has been completed. Instead of manually automating the entire project, we can quickly parameterize and personalize the process, which saves a lot of time.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "1. What do you mean by Selectors and Wildcards in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Wildcards are symbols that, similar to SQL, allow you to substitute 0/more characters in a string. They're usually employed when a selector's attributes are changing dynamically.   The following are used as wildcards:\nAsterisk (*) - can be used to replace one or more characters.\nQuestion Mark (?) - A single character is replaced by a question mark (?).\nIn the form of an XML fragment, selectors are used to store the characteristics of a GUI element and its parents.  Asterisk (*)  Question Mark (?) ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. In what aspects does UiPath differ from its competition Blue Prism?",
        "answer": "  Context UiPath Blue Prism\nProgramming Language Used Visual Basic is used here. C# is used here.\nControl Room It has a web-based control room that can be viewed from any computer with a browser. It includes client-based servers as well as a control room that can only be accessed through specific apps.\nDebugging Debugging is less efficient as compared to Blue Prism. UiPath does not allow users to make changes while it is being debugged. It allows users to interact with variables in a dynamic manner to remove the errors.\nAccess It has both mobile and desktop access. It has only desktop access.\nFlow Capture It has a macro recording feature enabled i.e., it can wait automatically for objects on web pages. It does not have a macro recording feature enabled. It requires a “Document Loader” action to wait for objects on web pages. Context UiPath Blue Prism\nProgramming Language Used Visual Basic is used here. C# is used here.\nControl Room It has a web-based control room that can be viewed from any computer with a browser. It includes client-based servers as well as a control room that can only be accessed through specific apps.\nDebugging Debugging is less efficient as compared to Blue Prism. UiPath does not allow users to make changes while it is being debugged. It allows users to interact with variables in a dynamic manner to remove the errors.\nAccess It has both mobile and desktop access. It has only desktop access.\nFlow Capture It has a macro recording feature enabled i.e., it can wait automatically for objects on web pages. It does not have a macro recording feature enabled. It requires a “Document Loader” action to wait for objects on web pages. Context UiPath Blue Prism Context UiPath Blue Prism Context UiPath Blue Prism Programming Language Used Visual Basic is used here. C# is used here.\nControl Room It has a web-based control room that can be viewed from any computer with a browser. It includes client-based servers as well as a control room that can only be accessed through specific apps.\nDebugging Debugging is less efficient as compared to Blue Prism. UiPath does not allow users to make changes while it is being debugged. It allows users to interact with variables in a dynamic manner to remove the errors.\nAccess It has both mobile and desktop access. It has only desktop access.\nFlow Capture It has a macro recording feature enabled i.e., it can wait automatically for objects on web pages. It does not have a macro recording feature enabled. It requires a “Document Loader” action to wait for objects on web pages. Programming Language Used Visual Basic is used here. C# is used here. Programming Language Used Visual Basic is used here. C# is used here. Control Room It has a web-based control room that can be viewed from any computer with a browser. It includes client-based servers as well as a control room that can only be accessed through specific apps. Control Room It has a web-based control room that can be viewed from any computer with a browser. It includes client-based servers as well as a control room that can only be accessed through specific apps. Debugging Debugging is less efficient as compared to Blue Prism. UiPath does not allow users to make changes while it is being debugged. It allows users to interact with variables in a dynamic manner to remove the errors. Debugging Debugging is less efficient as compared to Blue Prism. UiPath does not allow users to make changes while it is being debugged. It allows users to interact with variables in a dynamic manner to remove the errors. Access It has both mobile and desktop access. It has only desktop access. Access It has both mobile and desktop access. It has only desktop access. Flow Capture It has a macro recording feature enabled i.e., it can wait automatically for objects on web pages. It does not have a macro recording feature enabled. It requires a “Document Loader” action to wait for objects on web pages. Flow Capture It has a macro recording feature enabled i.e., it can wait automatically for objects on web pages. It does not have a macro recording feature enabled. It requires a “Document Loader” action to wait for objects on web pages.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. Explain the different types of recording available in UiPath.",
        "answer": "The following recording options are available in UiPath:   Basic: Basic recording is primarily utilized for single activities because it generates a full selection for each one.\nDesktop: Desktop recording is mostly utilized for all types of desktop programmes because it generates container activities and partial selections for each contained activity.\nWeb: This option is usually used in web programmes and browsers to record. This is due to the fact that it generates container activities by default, which use the Simulate Type/Click input technique.\nImage: This recording option is ideally suited for virtualized systems like Citrix, SAP, VNC, and virtual machines (VMs). It is, however, limited to text, keyboard, and image automation only.\nNative Citrix: It is meant for Citrix-virtualized desktops and apps.\nComputer Vision: It may be used to automate the design of computer vision-based workflows. Basic: Basic recording is primarily utilized for single activities because it generates a full selection for each one. Basic: Desktop: Desktop recording is mostly utilized for all types of desktop programmes because it generates container activities and partial selections for each contained activity. Desktop: Web: This option is usually used in web programmes and browsers to record. This is due to the fact that it generates container activities by default, which use the Simulate Type/Click input technique. Web: Image: This recording option is ideally suited for virtualized systems like Citrix, SAP, VNC, and virtual machines (VMs). It is, however, limited to text, keyboard, and image automation only. Image: Native Citrix: It is meant for Citrix-virtualized desktops and apps. Native Citrix: Computer Vision: It may be used to automate the design of computer vision-based workflows. Computer Vision:",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. What do you mean by “assign activity” in the context of UiPath?",
        "answer": "In UiPath, the assign activity is mostly used to assign values to variables. When we wish to alter the value of a variable, we usually use this action. This activity also comes in handy when we need to add a loop to our project. For instance, in the loop, incrementing the value of a variable. By default, the activity is included in the Favorites group. Using the 'Right-click' and then 'Remove' options, we can easily remove it. We have two alternatives when it comes to assigning activities: We can store values in the existing variable after adding the value.\nWe can store values in any other array after adding the value. We can store values in the existing variable after adding the value. We can store values in any other array after adding the value.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. What is the difference between chatbot and robotic process automation?",
        "answer": "The distinction between a chatbot and an RPA engine is comparable to that between a mouse and a mammoth.   ChatBot - A bot that is programmed to converse with a user (human) in a human-like manner. Make a request and advise backend systems to offer a request, or recommend a pre-learned remedy to a specific problem the user is experiencing.\nRPA (Robotic Process Automation) - It is a bot that is programmed to automate a manual business process such as performing a job or activity inside a business function. HR, Finance, and Procurement are examples of business functions. A chatbot can be used to supply data into an RPA engine, but it cannot replace the RPA engine's functions. ChatBot  RPA (Robotic Process Automation)",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. Differentiate between Traditional Automation and Robotic Process Automation.",
        "answer": "Following are the differences between Traditional Automation and Robotic Process Automation:   Traditional IT automation takes a long time and involves a lot of labour, time, effort, and money.\nRPA is a quick fix for generating improvements right away.\nTraditional automation and RPA both require sound strategy and preparation, but RPA is easier to implement.\nWhile both strive for the same goal of automation, RPA is more efficient, better, and less expensive than classical automation. As a result, traditional automation is a strategic decision, while RPA is a tactical decision.\nIn short, if you have the luxury of time and money, classical automation is the way to go. If you're pressed for time or money in your business, RPA is the way to go. Traditional IT automation takes a long time and involves a lot of labour, time, effort, and money. RPA is a quick fix for generating improvements right away. Traditional automation and RPA both require sound strategy and preparation, but RPA is easier to implement. While both strive for the same goal of automation, RPA is more efficient, better, and less expensive than classical automation. As a result, traditional automation is a strategic decision, while RPA is a tactical decision. In short, if you have the luxury of time and money, classical automation is the way to go. If you're pressed for time or money in your business, RPA is the way to go.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. What do you mean by thin and thick clients? Differentiate between them.",
        "answer": "Thin clients: A thin client is a computer system that operates on a server. They operate by connecting to a distant server-based environment, which stores the majority of apps and data. The majority of the tasks, such as computations and calculations, are handled by the server. When it comes to security threats, they are more secure than thick client systems. Because there are centralised servers in thin clients, system management is considerably easier. With the help of centralization, hardware may be optimised, and software maintenance is significantly easy.\nThick clients: A thick client is a system that can connect to the server even if it is not connected to the internet. Clients who are overweight are referred to as \"heavy\" or \"fat.\" Thick clients aren't reliant on the server's apps. They have their own software programmes and operating system. They have a lot of flexibility as well as a lot of server capacity. Thick clients are more vulnerable to security risks than thin clients. Thin clients  Thick clients:   Thin Client Thick Client\nThe installation of thin clients is done through a web browser. The installation of thick clients is done locally.\nHandheld devices make use of thin clients.  Thick clients are used in customization systems.\nThe server handles all of the processing in thin clients. Thick clients consume more computer resources than thin clients.\nWhen compared to thick clients, thin clients are much easier to deploy. Deploying thick clients is more expensive.\nFrom the server's perspective, data verification is required.  Client-side data verification is performed.\nIt can't be interfaced with anything else. It is more durable than thin clients and can be interfaced with other devices.\nThin clients necessitate constant communication with the server. Thick clients communicate with the server at predetermined intervals.\nIt poses less security risks.  When compared to thin clients, it poses a greater security risk. Thin Client Thick Client\nThe installation of thin clients is done through a web browser. The installation of thick clients is done locally.\nHandheld devices make use of thin clients.  Thick clients are used in customization systems.\nThe server handles all of the processing in thin clients. Thick clients consume more computer resources than thin clients.\nWhen compared to thick clients, thin clients are much easier to deploy. Deploying thick clients is more expensive.\nFrom the server's perspective, data verification is required.  Client-side data verification is performed.\nIt can't be interfaced with anything else. It is more durable than thin clients and can be interfaced with other devices.\nThin clients necessitate constant communication with the server. Thick clients communicate with the server at predetermined intervals.\nIt poses less security risks.  When compared to thin clients, it poses a greater security risk. Thin Client Thick Client Thin Client Thick Client Thin Client Thick Client The installation of thin clients is done through a web browser. The installation of thick clients is done locally.\nHandheld devices make use of thin clients.  Thick clients are used in customization systems.\nThe server handles all of the processing in thin clients. Thick clients consume more computer resources than thin clients.\nWhen compared to thick clients, thin clients are much easier to deploy. Deploying thick clients is more expensive.\nFrom the server's perspective, data verification is required.  Client-side data verification is performed.\nIt can't be interfaced with anything else. It is more durable than thin clients and can be interfaced with other devices.\nThin clients necessitate constant communication with the server. Thick clients communicate with the server at predetermined intervals.\nIt poses less security risks.  When compared to thin clients, it poses a greater security risk. The installation of thin clients is done through a web browser. The installation of thick clients is done locally. The installation of thin clients is done through a web browser. The installation of thick clients is done locally. Handheld devices make use of thin clients.  Thick clients are used in customization systems. Handheld devices make use of thin clients. Thick clients are used in customization systems. The server handles all of the processing in thin clients. Thick clients consume more computer resources than thin clients. The server handles all of the processing in thin clients. Thick clients consume more computer resources than thin clients. When compared to thick clients, thin clients are much easier to deploy. Deploying thick clients is more expensive. When compared to thick clients, thin clients are much easier to deploy. Deploying thick clients is more expensive. From the server's perspective, data verification is required.  Client-side data verification is performed. From the server's perspective, data verification is required. Client-side data verification is performed. It can't be interfaced with anything else. It is more durable than thin clients and can be interfaced with other devices. It can't be interfaced with anything else. It is more durable than thin clients and can be interfaced with other devices. Thin clients necessitate constant communication with the server. Thick clients communicate with the server at predetermined intervals. Thin clients necessitate constant communication with the server. Thick clients communicate with the server at predetermined intervals. It poses less security risks.  When compared to thin clients, it poses a greater security risk. It poses less security risks. When compared to thin clients, it poses a greater security risk.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. Can we run multiple instances of the same process with one robot in one system simultaneously in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Yes, it can run the same process in two robots at the same time if each system is registered as a separate robot. On a machine running the Windows Server operating system: All Robots can perform the same process at the same time; \nAll Robots can perform the different processes at the same time; All Robots can perform the same process at the same time; All Robots can perform the different processes at the same time; They are often referred to as high-density robots.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. What do you mean by Exception Handling and what are the main options in Exception Handling in UiPath?",
        "answer": "The practice of dealing with or addressing problems observed in various UiPath tasks is known as exception handling.   The following are the main options for managing exceptions: Rethrow: When we wish to conduct actions before an exception is thrown, we use rethrow.\nTerminate Workflow: It is used when a job finds an issue and we want to stop the entire workflow from running.\nThrow: When we wish to throw an error before performing any action, we use this method.\nTry Catch: It is mostly used to deal with exceptions. The try block contains a list of activities that may fail during execution. Furthermore, the tasks to be performed once an exception occurs are contained within the catch block. Rethrow: When we wish to conduct actions before an exception is thrown, we use rethrow. Rethrow: Terminate Workflow: It is used when a job finds an issue and we want to stop the entire workflow from running. Terminate Workflow: Throw: When we wish to throw an error before performing any action, we use this method. Throw: Try Catch: It is mostly used to deal with exceptions. The try block contains a list of activities that may fail during execution. Furthermore, the tasks to be performed once an exception occurs are contained within the catch block. Try Catch:",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. When should one choose System Integration over RPA?",
        "answer": "If the return on investment (ROI) is better than installing RPA, one should favor system integration. However, that circumstance will appear in only a few projects.   If one works in a local area and uses similar platforms/software, they should consider integrating your systems. System integration will almost certainly necessitate full access to the back-end scripts, and the deployment duration will almost certainly be longer than RPA. If one works in back-office operations, one may notice that different platforms, such as legacy, GUI, and web-based, are all utilized in tandem. System integration becomes more complicated as a result of this.\nRPA software, on the other hand, is platform agnostic. They might also be configured from the front end on any platform. RPA developers are easier to train or find, and the schedule is shorter. As a result, using RPA is a better option. ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "11. What do you mean by tracing and how do you enable it in UiPath?",
        "answer": "UiPath creates log files by default, which track Studio and Robot activities. The Open Logs button on the Execute ribbon tab can be used to access these logs.\nMore information on automation is required for difficult issues. Tracing must be enabled in order to collect them.\nTracing in UiPath Studio produces an .etl file. It is used to log high-frequency events when tracking the performance of an operating system and contains binary log data at the trace level, such as disk accesses or page faults.  ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "12. Differentiate between screen scraping and data scraping in UiPath.",
        "answer": "Screen Scraping Data Scraping \nNon-structural data is extracted through screen scraping. Data Scraping is a technique for extracting structural data.\nIt saves the scraped data as a string. It stores scraped data in a data table.\nImages and PDFs can be used to extract or collect data. It is unable to extract data from PDF or picture files.\nIt is difficult to extract data into databases or spreadsheets. It can extract data quickly and easily into databases or spreadsheets. Screen Scraping Data Scraping \nNon-structural data is extracted through screen scraping. Data Scraping is a technique for extracting structural data.\nIt saves the scraped data as a string. It stores scraped data in a data table.\nImages and PDFs can be used to extract or collect data. It is unable to extract data from PDF or picture files.\nIt is difficult to extract data into databases or spreadsheets. It can extract data quickly and easily into databases or spreadsheets. Screen Scraping Data Scraping Screen Scraping Data Scraping Screen Scraping Data Scraping Non-structural data is extracted through screen scraping. Data Scraping is a technique for extracting structural data.\nIt saves the scraped data as a string. It stores scraped data in a data table.\nImages and PDFs can be used to extract or collect data. It is unable to extract data from PDF or picture files.\nIt is difficult to extract data into databases or spreadsheets. It can extract data quickly and easily into databases or spreadsheets. Non-structural data is extracted through screen scraping. Data Scraping is a technique for extracting structural data. Non-structural data is extracted through screen scraping. Data Scraping is a technique for extracting structural data. It saves the scraped data as a string. It stores scraped data in a data table. It saves the scraped data as a string. It stores scraped data in a data table. Images and PDFs can be used to extract or collect data. It is unable to extract data from PDF or picture files. Images and PDFs can be used to extract or collect data. It is unable to extract data from PDF or picture files. It is difficult to extract data into databases or spreadsheets. It can extract data quickly and easily into databases or spreadsheets. It is difficult to extract data into databases or spreadsheets. It can extract data quickly and easily into databases or spreadsheets.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "13. Differentiate between Mainframe and Non-Mainframe Applications.",
        "answer": "Mainframe Applications: Mainframe Applications: It's a single-screen application with a keyboard interface.\nBlue Prism has a different set of in-built commands dedicated to mainframe applications. It's a single-screen application with a keyboard interface. Blue Prism has a different set of in-built commands dedicated to mainframe applications. Non-Mainframe Applications: Non-Mainframe Applications: It includes more than one screen.\nControl is passed from one screen to the next. It includes more than one screen. Control is passed from one screen to the next.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "14. Differentiate between UiPath and Selenium.",
        "answer": "Selenium is built primarily for testing web applications and web pages; it is impossible to interact with numerous applications in selenium and use one application's result as an input for another. It is completely incompatible with virtual environments such as Citrix and others. While UiPath is an RPA solution that can be used to automate any existing software process and replace any activity that can be done by a human. Selenium   As a result, we can argue that RPA is the next step in the evolution of existing automation systems. It enables anyone with little or no software programming experience to create a complicated rules-based procedure. You can use UiPath to perform whatever that Selenium can do, but vice versa is not possible.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "15. How should a RPA developer address runtime exceptions in the workflows?",
        "answer": "RPA developers should use one of the following methods to address runtime exceptions in the workflows: By keeping track of any exceptions that occur.\nInside the Catch blocks, employing automatic recovery sequences.\nWhen executing external workflow files, try/catch blocks are used. By keeping track of any exceptions that occur. Inside the Catch blocks, employing automatic recovery sequences. When executing external workflow files, try/catch blocks are used.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "16. What do you mean by Citrix Automation?",
        "answer": "  Citrix Technology is used to automate virtual computers. Consider a situation in which you need to connect to a server from your PC. When you try to access thserver now, you don't receive the main server; instead, you get a picture of the server's screen. Now, anytime you click on something, the corresponding image or pixel is delivered to the server. Then it is precisely clicked over there in the server. Citrix technology and UiPath can be used to automate these kinds of processes. With the use of recorders, UiPath attempts to deliver this automation.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "17. What do you mean by process, job, asset and queue in the context of UiPath?",
        "answer": "Processes- The Processes page allows users to create new processes, manage current processes, and build new processes from uploaded packages, as well as maintain all of your processes up to date with the latest package versions. Processes Queues are a form of storage container that may hold an infinite number of objects. Queue objects can be used to store a variety of data, such as invoices or client information. Other systems, such as SAP or Salesforce, are used to process this data. Queues Jobs- A job is a description of how a procedure is carried out on an UiPath Robot. It has the ability to start a job in either attended or unattended mode. Jobs Assets are variables or credentials that are regularly shared and can be used in various automation programmes. They let users store one-of-a-kind information that robots can access fast. Assets",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "18. Explain different types of automation in UiPath.",
        "answer": "  Excel Automation: For sorting, removing, retrieving, and analyzing data, UiPath is a useful tool. Data migration and integration into platforms are straightforward. StudioX has a strong Microsoft Excel interface and comes with various activities that automate Excel chores.\nFile Automation: It refers to the automation of file and folder-related actions on your computer, such as creating, renaming, and copying files and folders. StudioX comes with a number of activities that help you automate actions involving files and folders.\nCSV Automation: It is used to attach data to CSV files or to get data from them. Add the CSV actions to the Use Excel File activity, which defines the Excel file that will be used to transport data from CSV to Excel.\nMail Automation: Task automation is possible with emails from Outlook desktop, Gmail, and Outlook 365. By using Outlook 365, Gmail, or the \"Use Desktop Outlook App\" action, users can create activities that use data from the account inside the resource activity.\nWord Automation: The most typical tasks in Word documents may be automated using Word automation.\nPowerPoint Automation: This allows the user to automate some of the most popular PowerPoint actions. Add a ‘Use PowerPoint Presentation' action to the presentation, and then add the Presentation activities to automate inside Use PowerPoint Presentation. Excel Automation: For sorting, removing, retrieving, and analyzing data, UiPath is a useful tool. Data migration and integration into platforms are straightforward. StudioX has a strong Microsoft Excel interface and comes with various activities that automate Excel chores. Excel Automation: File Automation: It refers to the automation of file and folder-related actions on your computer, such as creating, renaming, and copying files and folders. StudioX comes with a number of activities that help you automate actions involving files and folders. File Automation: CSV Automation: It is used to attach data to CSV files or to get data from them. Add the CSV actions to the Use Excel File activity, which defines the Excel file that will be used to transport data from CSV to Excel. CSV Automation: Mail Automation: Task automation is possible with emails from Outlook desktop, Gmail, and Outlook 365. By using Outlook 365, Gmail, or the \"Use Desktop Outlook App\" action, users can create activities that use data from the account inside the resource activity. Mail Automation: Word Automation: The most typical tasks in Word documents may be automated using Word automation. Word Automation: PowerPoint Automation: This allows the user to automate some of the most popular PowerPoint actions. Add a ‘Use PowerPoint Presentation' action to the presentation, and then add the Presentation activities to automate inside Use PowerPoint Presentation. PowerPoint Automation: Use PowerPoint Presentation Conclusion: The RPA tool UiPath is well-known. Its popularity has expanded over time, and it is now used by organizations all around the world. UiPath helps firms automate their business operations by allowing IT teams to set up software robots that collect and evaluate data in a range of applications. People that learn UiPath will have a lot of opportunities in the future. Useful Resources: Useful Resources: UiPath Documentation\nRobot Framework Interview Questions\nTechnical Interview Questions UiPath Documentation UiPath Documentation Robot Framework Interview Questions Robot Framework Interview Questions Technical Interview Questions Technical Interview Questions",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "19. Differentiate between RPA and Test Automation.",
        "answer": "Robotic Process Automation (RPA) is a software robot that can do tasks similar to those performed by humans. These software robots are designed and deployed using RPA techniques. These tools use pre-defined activities and business rules to execute a set of tasks, transactions, and processes across multiple software platforms autonomously. RPA can achieve the required outcome without the need for human intervention. Robotic Process Automation (RPA) Test Automation is a software testing process that employs specialized tools to manage the execution of tests. It also compares the actual results to the ones expected. Test automation is carried out automatically, with little or no involvement from the test engineer. It's a key stage in the development process for adding more testing that's tough to do manually. Test Automation   Robotic Process Automation Test Automation\nRPA automates business procedures that are repeated over and over. Test automation is the process of automating repetitive test cases.\nRPA may be used to automate both product and business activities. Only the product and its features can be subjected to test automation.\nTo automate processes, RPA offers a drag-and-drop feature. As a result, programming skills are not that essential. Test automation necessitates programming or coding expertise.\nOnly one production environment is required for RPA. Test automation is used in a variety of situations (i.e., QA, Production, Performance, UAT).\nRPA is compatible with a wide range of software platforms. With constrained software environments, test automation can be used. Selenium, for example, is limited to web apps.\nRPA aids in the automation of tasks such as data entry, loan processing, form filling, and so on. Only test cases can be automated with the help of test automation.\nRPA aids in the reduction of human labour. Test automation shortens the time it takes to complete a test.\nRPA is a type of virtual workforce. Test automation is like having a personal helper.\nAt their most basic level, RPA tools can be thought of as testing tools. These tools, however, are not as effective as test automation tools. Robotic Process Automation cannot be done with test automation technologies.\nRPA can be used to automate anything that is structured. As a result, not every testing product on the market can be used as an RPA tool. The use of test automation tools is limited by the fact that they require software to function.\nMany RPA technologies include an AI engine that can process data similarly to a human. Only what is coded in test automation can be executed.\n\"Blueprism, Automation Anywhere, UiPath, and NICE, among others\" are some of the most prominent RPA tools. \"Selenium, HP - UFT/QTP, IBM - RFT, Appium, Jira, and others\" are some common test automation tools. Robotic Process Automation Test Automation\nRPA automates business procedures that are repeated over and over. Test automation is the process of automating repetitive test cases.\nRPA may be used to automate both product and business activities. Only the product and its features can be subjected to test automation.\nTo automate processes, RPA offers a drag-and-drop feature. As a result, programming skills are not that essential. Test automation necessitates programming or coding expertise.\nOnly one production environment is required for RPA. Test automation is used in a variety of situations (i.e., QA, Production, Performance, UAT).\nRPA is compatible with a wide range of software platforms. With constrained software environments, test automation can be used. Selenium, for example, is limited to web apps.\nRPA aids in the automation of tasks such as data entry, loan processing, form filling, and so on. Only test cases can be automated with the help of test automation.\nRPA aids in the reduction of human labour. Test automation shortens the time it takes to complete a test.\nRPA is a type of virtual workforce. Test automation is like having a personal helper.\nAt their most basic level, RPA tools can be thought of as testing tools. These tools, however, are not as effective as test automation tools. Robotic Process Automation cannot be done with test automation technologies.\nRPA can be used to automate anything that is structured. As a result, not every testing product on the market can be used as an RPA tool. The use of test automation tools is limited by the fact that they require software to function.\nMany RPA technologies include an AI engine that can process data similarly to a human. Only what is coded in test automation can be executed.\n\"Blueprism, Automation Anywhere, UiPath, and NICE, among others\" are some of the most prominent RPA tools. \"Selenium, HP - UFT/QTP, IBM - RFT, Appium, Jira, and others\" are some common test automation tools. Robotic Process Automation Test Automation Robotic Process Automation Test Automation Robotic Process Automation Test Automation RPA automates business procedures that are repeated over and over. Test automation is the process of automating repetitive test cases.\nRPA may be used to automate both product and business activities. Only the product and its features can be subjected to test automation.\nTo automate processes, RPA offers a drag-and-drop feature. As a result, programming skills are not that essential. Test automation necessitates programming or coding expertise.\nOnly one production environment is required for RPA. Test automation is used in a variety of situations (i.e., QA, Production, Performance, UAT).\nRPA is compatible with a wide range of software platforms. With constrained software environments, test automation can be used. Selenium, for example, is limited to web apps.\nRPA aids in the automation of tasks such as data entry, loan processing, form filling, and so on. Only test cases can be automated with the help of test automation.\nRPA aids in the reduction of human labour. Test automation shortens the time it takes to complete a test.\nRPA is a type of virtual workforce. Test automation is like having a personal helper.\nAt their most basic level, RPA tools can be thought of as testing tools. These tools, however, are not as effective as test automation tools. Robotic Process Automation cannot be done with test automation technologies.\nRPA can be used to automate anything that is structured. As a result, not every testing product on the market can be used as an RPA tool. The use of test automation tools is limited by the fact that they require software to function.\nMany RPA technologies include an AI engine that can process data similarly to a human. Only what is coded in test automation can be executed.\n\"Blueprism, Automation Anywhere, UiPath, and NICE, among others\" are some of the most prominent RPA tools. \"Selenium, HP - UFT/QTP, IBM - RFT, Appium, Jira, and others\" are some common test automation tools. RPA automates business procedures that are repeated over and over. Test automation is the process of automating repetitive test cases. RPA automates business procedures that are repeated over and over. Test automation is the process of automating repetitive test cases. RPA may be used to automate both product and business activities. Only the product and its features can be subjected to test automation. RPA may be used to automate both product and business activities. Only the product and its features can be subjected to test automation. To automate processes, RPA offers a drag-and-drop feature. As a result, programming skills are not that essential. Test automation necessitates programming or coding expertise. To automate processes, RPA offers a drag-and-drop feature. As a result, programming skills are not that essential. Test automation necessitates programming or coding expertise. Only one production environment is required for RPA. Test automation is used in a variety of situations (i.e., QA, Production, Performance, UAT). Only one production environment is required for RPA. Test automation is used in a variety of situations (i.e., QA, Production, Performance, UAT). RPA is compatible with a wide range of software platforms. With constrained software environments, test automation can be used. Selenium, for example, is limited to web apps. RPA is compatible with a wide range of software platforms. With constrained software environments, test automation can be used. Selenium, for example, is limited to web apps. RPA aids in the automation of tasks such as data entry, loan processing, form filling, and so on. Only test cases can be automated with the help of test automation. RPA aids in the automation of tasks such as data entry, loan processing, form filling, and so on. Only test cases can be automated with the help of test automation. RPA aids in the reduction of human labour. Test automation shortens the time it takes to complete a test. RPA aids in the reduction of human labour. Test automation shortens the time it takes to complete a test. RPA is a type of virtual workforce. Test automation is like having a personal helper. RPA is a type of virtual workforce. Test automation is like having a personal helper. At their most basic level, RPA tools can be thought of as testing tools. These tools, however, are not as effective as test automation tools. Robotic Process Automation cannot be done with test automation technologies. At their most basic level, RPA tools can be thought of as testing tools. These tools, however, are not as effective as test automation tools. Robotic Process Automation cannot be done with test automation technologies. RPA can be used to automate anything that is structured. As a result, not every testing product on the market can be used as an RPA tool. The use of test automation tools is limited by the fact that they require software to function. RPA can be used to automate anything that is structured. As a result, not every testing product on the market can be used as an RPA tool. The use of test automation tools is limited by the fact that they require software to function. Many RPA technologies include an AI engine that can process data similarly to a human. Only what is coded in test automation can be executed. Many RPA technologies include an AI engine that can process data similarly to a human. Only what is coded in test automation can be executed. \"Blueprism, Automation Anywhere, UiPath, and NICE, among others\" are some of the most prominent RPA tools. \"Selenium, HP - UFT/QTP, IBM - RFT, Appium, Jira, and others\" are some common test automation tools. \"Blueprism, Automation Anywhere, UiPath, and NICE, among others\" are some of the most prominent RPA tools. \"Selenium, HP - UFT/QTP, IBM - RFT, Appium, Jira, and others\" are some common test automation tools.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "20. Explain UiPath Architecture.",
        "answer": "The UiPath architecture is made up of three layers, including:   Client Layer: This layer comprises UiPath components that users can interact with. UiPath Studio, UiPath Agent, Robots, Browsers, and Executors are some of the examples. These components can be used to build and develop automation tasks. UiPath bots then carry out the tasks that have been created. The layer is sometimes referred to as the presentation layer. Client Layer Server Layer: This layer displays all of the server-related information. The UiPath Orchestrator is located on this tier. The full project is published to the server once the UiPath bots have been constructed and can execute tasks without issues. The project can be easily executed on several platforms thanks to an Orchestrator. The Orchestrator is in charge of the entire project and assists us in meeting service levels and schedules. Server Layer Persistence Layer: Database servers make up the majority of the persistency layer. The layer is used to hold UiPath bot configuration information. It also organizes and regulates queues, as well as the tasks currently in them.\nData from different users, logging information, associated robots, assigned tasks, asset details, and so on are all included in the configuration details. Users often enter the needed details in the Orchestrator. Persistence Layer ",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "1. Is it easy to learn UiPath?",
        "answer": "UiPath is simple to use and features drag-and-drop activity functionality, so you can learn it without paying for a course or tutor. The best thing is that UiPath provides a Community Edition that is free for life and includes most of the features of the Studio version. It's a lot easier to learn than programming because it comes with a lot of helpful tools and GUI components, as well as active forums and a lot of training information.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. Is RPA a good career choice?",
        "answer": "RPA is a fantastic career choice since more and more firms are turning to automation to save money, and they can't find enough employees with good RPA abilities to fill their positions. As a result, RPA salaries have risen faster than those in other IT disciplines.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. Is RPA really worth learning?",
        "answer": "Yes, RPA is worth learning. First of all, RPA can replace 5 to 10 human workers, resulting in a higher return on investment. Secondly, RPA automates dull and repetitive operations, freeing up human workers to focus on more productive and revenue-generating duties. Thirdly, RPA is more accurate and has a better throughput than human workers.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. Is RPA a hype?",
        "answer": "No, RPA is not a hype. RPA is the fastest-growing section of the global enterprise software market, with projections predicting that 85%t of large and very large companies will use it in some way. They anticipate that RPA expanded by 63% to $846 million in 2018, with the three major providers expanding by more than 40%.",
        "reference": "interviewbit.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "1) What is UiPath?",
        "answer": "UiPath is one of the most popular RPA tools, which provides end-to-end automation solutions. It helps organizations to automate their repetitive and recurring processes in an efficient way. The tool has advanced robotic power capabilities that help organization automate their redundant business processes efficiently. It is an open platform RPA tool consisting of several built-in, customizable integrations with a combination of technologies such as BPM, ERP, and AI.\nUiPath tool is currently the main product of UiPath, a leading RPA provider in the automation industry.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "2) What does RPA mean?",
        "answer": "RPA is the short form of \"Robotic Process Automation\". RPA is a special kind of automation technique in which software robots perform a human's tasks. These tasks generally include repetitive, rule-based, and manual processes. The technique helps organizations automate their digital processes across various applications and systems without changing the existing systems or IT infrastructure.\nRobotic: Set of codes that acts like a robot and mimic human actions.\nProcess: Sequence of steps that creates a meaningful activity is known as the process.\nAutomation: The process performed by software robots without human interaction.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "3) Why is UiPath better than other RPA tools?",
        "answer": "UiPath is an enterprise computing solution that is uniquely designed to automate the business process. There are a wide variety of unique features and functionalities that are provided according to industry standards. The following are some options that make UiPath better compared to other RPA tools:\nADVERTISEMENT\nProcess Modelling\nDeployment Management\nChange Management\nRemote Execution\nAccess Control\nScheduling\nEnterprise-Level Security",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "4) What are the main components of UiPath?",
        "answer": "UiPath mainly consists of the following three components:\nUiPath Studio: It is a GUI dashboard used to create automation workflow. It contains various tools and options, making it a complete solution for designing workflow. Each workflow represents a particular type of job to perform.\nUiPath Robot: UiPath robots (also called bots) are the fundamental component of the UiPath tool. They are mainly used for the execution of automation workflows created in UiPath Studio. These robots can also be used to automatically start the execution of tasks in response to any specific activity that occurs on the system.\nUiPath Orchestrator: It is a web-based application that provides options to deploy, schedule, monitor, and manage UiPath robots in the environment. It is defined as the centralized platform used to manage/control software robots. It is the medium that connects UiPath Studio and UiPath robots.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "5) What are the types of workflows present in RPA UiPath?",
        "answer": "UiPath consists of the following workflow types:\nSequences: The sequence is defined as a small project that is most suitable for linear processes. It allows developers to switch from one activity to another easily. It can be reused again and again as many times as required.\nState Machine: A machine using a particular number of states for automation in the execution time is called the state machine. It can be switched from one state to another by triggering a specific action.\nFlowchart: Flowchart is a graphical representation of different processes to be automated. It is beneficial for building complex business tasks and connecting the activities in large projects. Flowcharts also help in the presentation of several branching of logical operators.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "Some of the main features of UiPath are:\nAccurate: UiPath works with accuracy even though there are several tasks to execute. Thus, it helps to automate tasks by eliminating errors.\nCode-Free: UiPath can be used for automating repetitive processes without the requirements of any programming or coding knowledge. Any automation workflow can be easily created using drag-drops or recording tools.\nConsistent: UiPath robots are consistent, and they can work with the same consistency even when there are hundreds or thousands of tasks to be performed.\nProductivity: Robots work faster as compared to humans. This reduces the overall time and increases productivity.\nEfficiency: UiPath robots are developed to work continuously without a break, with the same efficiency.\n\nCost-Cutting: Because UiPath uses software robots to perform automated tasks, it enables organizations to reduce manual workforce and overall cost to perform any task.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "There are two types of robots in UiPath:\nAttended: Attended robots operate on the same workstation as humans and helps them get their regular tasks done in an automated way. These robots are generally triggered by user events or actions. The attended robot cannot be used when we want to start processes from Orchestrator or when a screen is locked. We can start these types of robots directly from the Robot tray. Also, we can start them by using a particular command in Command Prompt. Attended robots should be run only when they are under human supervision.\nUnattended: Unattended robots are autonomous robots that do not require human supervision during the execution. They run unattended in virtual environments and can automate multiple tasks simultaneously. These types of robots contain all the capabilities of attended robots. They are also used for monitoring & scheduling tasks, remote execution, and offering support for process queue.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "8) What does the term 'UiPath Automation' mean?",
        "answer": "UiPath is one of the leading RPA tools explicitly developed for the automation process. It contains various tools and features to help automate business processes for organizations. UiPath automation is generally the term used to define that the processes are automated using the UiPath tool. The primary goal of UiPath automation is to assist humans in performing their daily tasks with ease.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "9) What is the main difference between Process Automation and Test Automation?",
        "answer": "Process Automation is used to automate processes that do not require human intervention. Besides, Test Automation is used for testing purposes during the automation process to check whether implemented cases are passed or failed.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "10) How is UiPath different from Selenium?",
        "answer": "Selenium is one of the popular testing tools that is mainly used to test websites and applications. It is not possible to integrate Selenium with other applications. Also, one cannot use Selenium to work with virtual environments like Citrix or others. On the other hand, UiPath is a leading RPA tool that is used to automate jobs performed by humans. UiPath allows developers to automate complex tasks with minimum coding knowledge.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "11) What are the main applications of UiPath?",
        "answer": "Few of the main applications of UiPath are as follows:\nData Extraction\nPerforming Financial Reporting and Closing\nGetting Market Reports\nMaintaining Customer Dashboard Data\nOrder Processing\nInvoice Generation\nData Capture and Manipulation\nData Entry\nEmail Sharing\nCollecting Information from Various Sources\nAutomating Daily Routine Tasks within the System",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "There are three layers in the UiPath architecture, such as:\nClient Layer: This layer contains such UiPath components that can be accessed by the users. For example, UiPath Studio, UiPath agent, Robots, Browsers, and executors. The user can use these components to design/develop automation tasks. The created tasks are then executed with the help of UiPath bots. Sometimes, the layer is also represented as the presentation layer.\nServer Layer: All the details based on the server are displayed on this layer. This layer contains the UiPath Orchestrator. When the UiPath bots are developed and can execute tasks without errors, the entire project is uploaded on the server. Because of an Orchestrator, the project can be easily run on several systems.\nThe Orchestrator handles the entire project and helps our project to meet service levels and timelines.\nPersistency Layer: The persistency layer mainly includes database servers. The layer is used to store configuration details of UiPath bots. It also manages and controls queues and the present tasks in these queues.\nThe configuration details include data of different users, logging information, corresponding robots, assigned tasks, asset details, etc. The specified details are usually entered by the users in the Orchestrator.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "13) What is the difference between screen scraping and data scraping in UiPath?",
        "answer": "The main differences between screen scraping and data scraping are tabulated below:\nScreen Scraping Data Scraping\nScreen scraping is used to extract non-structural data. Data scraping is generally used to extract structural data.\nIt keeps scraped information in a string. It keeps scraped information in a data table.\nIt can extract or collect data from images and PDFs. It cannot extract data from PDF files or images.\nIt cannot easily extract data into databases or excel. It can efficiently extract data into databases or excel.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "In UiPath, Citrix Automation used for operating and working on the virtual machines. The Citrix robotization in UiPath is the way to implement automation in the Citrix machines.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "15) How is UiPath different from Blue Prism?",
        "answer": "UiPath and Blue Prism are the popular RPA tools, but both have their features and user-interface. We can differentiate these tools in terms of the followings:\nIn term of UiPath Blue Prism\nProgramming Language It uses Visual Basic for coding. It uses C# for coding.\nControl Room It has a web-based control room that can be easily accessed using browsers. It has client-based servers and a control room that can only be accessed using particular applications.\nUses It is affordable and made for complex automation. It is easier to learn for individuals. One can operate it and use it easily.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "16) What are the arguments?",
        "answer": "The arguments in UiPath are mainly used when there is a requirement to pass data from one workflow to another. They are responsible for moving data between projects. These arguments follow a specific direction. For example- In, Out, In/Out.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "In UiPath, session variables are defined as particular to the one instance of any process. If multiple instances of the corresponding process continue simultaneously, they all will have the same session variables. However, the values for those session variables will be different.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "In UiPath, the generic variable is the kind of variable that can hold any variety of data types. For example - arrays, int, strings, and date formats, etc.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "19) What is the role of properties in UiPath?",
        "answer": "UiPath has a variety of activities that help us to automate desktop and web-based applications. Properties define such activities that are used for automating applications in the activity panel under UI automation. The basic properties of any project include ContinueOnError, Delay Before, Delay After, TimeoutMS, Target, and WaitForReady:\nContinueOnError: It is used when we want our automation continuously working even when the activity shows any error. Here, the 'False' is the default value. When an activity inside the 'try catch' is set to 'True', no error will be shown for the particular project.\nDelay Before: It is used to pause the automation before any specific activity.\nDelay After: It is used to pause the automation after any specific activity.\nTimeoutMS: It is used to find the element before an error is displayed.\nTarget: It is used to identify the element before an activity begins.\nWaitForReady: It is used to wait for the automation until the target is ready and before an activity is performed.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "In the context of UiPath, flow decisions and flow switches are the same. The one significant difference between them is that the flow switch has an extra option called 'flow step'. Each branch of the flow switch is defined as a flow step and is not just restricted by true or false branch.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "21) What does Branching mean?",
        "answer": "Branching in UiPath is generally defined as the 'condition'. The branching condition is used when there is an activity with multiple solutions after any specific condition. This branching allows the program to decide what behavior should be displayed in case of the selection of any particular condition.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "22) What is the function of sequence activity in UiPath?",
        "answer": "The sequence activity is a small project type responsible for allowing certain permissions to the path to move from one activity to another easily. In UiPath, the sequence activity is a single block activity, and these blocks are developed in such a way that they can be reused several times.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "Exception Handling is the process of dealing or handling errors found in different activities in UiPath.\nThe exception handling mainly has the following options:\nRethrow: It is used when we want to run activities before an exception is thrown.\nTerminate Workflow: It is used when a task encounters an error, and we want to shut down the execution of the entire workflow.\nThrow: It is applied when we want to throw an error before executing any step.\nTry Catch: It is mainly used to handle the exception. The set of activities that might fail during execution are placed inside the try block. Besides, the activities to perform after an exception takes place are placed inside the catch block.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "24) What are the types of recording options present in the UiPath tool?",
        "answer": "UiPath provides the following recording options:\nBasic: Because it generates a full selector for each activity, the basic recording is mainly used for single activities.\nDesktop: Because it generates container activities and partial selectors for each included activity, the desktop recording is mainly used for all types of desktop applications.\nWeb: This option is mostly used for recording in web apps and browsers. This is because it generates container activities and uses the Simulate Type/Click input method by default.\nImage: This recording option is best suitable for virtualized environments such as Citrix, SAP, VNC, and VMs. However, it is limited to only text, keyboard, and image automation.\nNative Citrix: It is designed for desktop and applications that are virtualized through Citrix technology.\nComputer Vision: It is suitable for automating designing workflows that use computer vision activities.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "25) What is the role of debugging?",
        "answer": "In UiPath, debugging is the process of analyzing the entire project and then finding and removing errors. It highlights the activities and functionalities of the project and enables us to check all the project details. It displays information in the output panel and makes it easier for us to remove errors. While debugging a project, UiPath displays breakpoints throughout the project that can be used to pause the execution at any specific point. The debugging makes the process of identifying and removing errors easier.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "In UiPath, variables are commonly used to store data. The data stored in variables can be easily changed or updated. Variables allow us to store data in various forms. UiPath has different data types, such as number, text, date, time, data tables, and universal value, etc.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "27) Why do we use flowchart activities in UiPath?",
        "answer": "The flowchart activities enable us to manage basic settings for any task in UiPath. We can use these activities for almost every type of automation project despite their length and complexity. Besides, flowcharts are used for segregating and building logical operations during the automation of complex business projects. Flowchart activities can be used to integrate necessary actions or functions in flowcharts during the automation process.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "28) Why the term 'assign activity' is used in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Assign activity in UiPath is mainly used for assigning the values to variables. This activity is mostly used when we want to change the value of the variable. Also, this activity helps in such cases when we want to implement a loop to our project. For example, incrementing the value of a variable in the loop. The activity remains in-built with the Favorites group by default. However, we can simply remove it by using 'Right-click' and then 'Remove' option.\nThere are two options that we can use by assign activity:\nAfter adding the value, we can store values in the existing variable.\nAfter adding the value, we can store values in any other array.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "The switch activity in UiPath is used to switch from one value to another based on the defined values in the expression. It uses switch integer argument as default. However, we can easily change it by going to the properties panel and selecting the required Type of Argument (TypeArgument). The activity is mainly helpful during the categorization of data based on the case number. For example, we can use this activity to save data into different spreadsheets or to sort through a list of user names.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "30) What are the steps to handle the credentials in UiPath?",
        "answer": "To handle credentials in UiPath, we need to follow the steps as listed below:\nUsing a credential manager on the corresponding window.\nStoring the details in Orchestrator as the credential variable type.\nUsing a built-in input boxing feature to get secure text activity.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "31) What is meant by the Package manager in UiPath?",
        "answer": "A package manager in UiPath is defined as the set of different elements that are helpful during the automation process. A package manager acts as the bundle that contains basic things of UiPath, such as frameworks, libraries, wrappers, etc.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "32) Why do we use break activity?",
        "answer": "UiPath provides an option to stop any specific loop at any chosen point using the 'break' activity. We can use that time to proceed with any other single activity or multiple activities as per the project's need.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "33) Why do we use 'do while' activity?",
        "answer": "The 'do while' activity is a condition used to execute any particular part of the automation project when the condition is true. If the specified condition doesn't meet, means the condition is false, the project exits the loop. It can be used to step through array elements in the automation project in UiPath. The activity is also useful to execute any specific activity multiple times. We can easily increment counters if we want to browse through array indices or when we want to step through a list of items.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "34) Why do we use the If activity?",
        "answer": "The 'If' activity is a combination of a statement and two different conditions. This activity is mainly used to compare two values or two activities based on specified conditions. In this process, if the condition satisfies, it returns true; otherwise, it returns false. The first condition is executed only when the particular statement is true, while the second (the statement inside the else block) is executed when the statement is false. The 'If' activity is beneficial in cases where we want to make decisions based on the values of the variables.\nADVERTISEMENT",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "35) What is the use of For Each activity?",
        "answer": "For Each activity in UiPath is used to step through arrays, lists, data tables, or other types of collections. It enables us to iterate through the data and then individually process each piece of the information.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "36) What are the supported OCR (Optical Character Recognition) engines in UiPath?",
        "answer": "The following are the supported OCR engines in UiPath:\nGoogle\nMicrosoft\nAbby",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "37) Is there any option for automatic recording in UiPath?",
        "answer": "Yes, UiPath allows us to record the actions and activities performed on the system automatically. The automatic recording feature provides a variety of options that we can use to customize the project easily. It generates a skeleton of the entire performed process. Because we can easily parameterize and customize the process, it saves a lot of time instead of manually automating the entire project.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "38) What is meant by the term 'Packaging' in UiPath?",
        "answer": "In UiPath, the term packaging is used to archive and send automation packages to software robots so that these packages can be executed. While working on UiPath, the projects are generally displayed on the packages page in the orchestrator field. We can distribute these packages to the connected robots by assigning them to specific robots in the environment. If we are not connected to the orchestrator, the packages will get stored locally in the UiPath Studio feed by default.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "The concept of Control Flow is derived from computer science, which is used to define the order or the sequence of actions executed in automation. To achieve a well-formatted Control Flow, we are required to use appropriate variables and activities during the automation process.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    },
    {
        "question": "40) What is the use of Delay activity?",
        "answer": "We can use the delay activity to pause or stop the automation for any specific period. The delay activity is mainly used when we require some time for any specific application or activity to be processed. At that particular delay period, we can process some other activities of the automation process.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "uipath"
    }
]